## **PROFILE**

Selfless and a hardworking team player with skillset ranging from app / game development to web development.

I am a self-taught full stack engineer with 3+ years' experience as a Software Engineer and a strong desire to do and also learn more.

#### CONTACT

PHONE: 0578876149

WEBSITE:

https://calebmantey.github.io/portfolio/

EMAIL: manteycaleb@gmail.com

#### **HOBBIES**

Playing Video Games Reading Watching Sports

# MANTEY CALEB EDEM KOMLA

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## **EDUCATION**

## **UNIVERSITY OF MINES AND TECHNOLOGY**

2015 - 2019

B.Sc. Geomatic Engineering

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

## GRAF ROBOTICS CHALLENGE (September, 2012 / September, 2013)

Winners / First Runner Ups

## UNIVERSITY OF MINES & TECHNOLOGY NUGS AWARD (March, 2018)

Best Student in Tech

# UNIVERSITY OF MINES & TECHNOLOGY Innovation & Career Fair (April, 2018)

First Runner Ups

## UNIVERSITY OF MINES & TECHNOLOGY EXCELLENCE AWARD (April, 2018)

Most Innovative Student

## HACKLABGH HACKATHON (April, 2018 / April, 2019)

First Runner Ups / Best Solution Education Category Award

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## ENCODEV LABS - SOFTWARE ENGINEER (September, 2020 – To Date)

**Task:** Developing, planning, architecting and providing support for various software projects.

Role: Software Engineer

#### SOKO AERIAL – SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (September, 2019 – July, 2020)

**Task:** Creating military experiences for training new recruits and enhancing military tech through the use of AR and VR.

Role: Full Stack Developer / Senior Virtual and Augmented Reality

Developer / Unity3d Developer

## STANBIC BANK - SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (May, 2019 - August, 2019)

**Task:** Developing banking web apps and integrating with 3<sup>rd</sup> party

systems

Role: Full Stack Developer

## **SKILLS**

Html, Css, C#, React / React Native , NodeJs (Express), Electron, ruby, ruby on rails, JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, Unity3d Game , NestJs Development, Augmented and Virtual Reality, framework7, cordova.